<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cdl:cdl
    targetNamespace="http://cddlm.org/component-model-example"
    xmlns="http://cddlm.org/component-model-example"
    xmlns:cdl="http://www.gridforum.org/namespaces/2005/02/cddlm/CDL-1.0"
    xmlns:cmp="http://www.gridforum.org/cddlm/components/2005/02"
    xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <cdl:configuration>
    <PosixApplication>
      <cmp:CodeBase>com.example.cddlm.BasicPosixComponent</cmp:CodeBase>
      <cmp:CommandPath>com.example.cddlm.BasicPosixComponent</cmp:CommandPath>
      <cdl:documentation>Jun will fix this element shortly.</cdl:documentation>
    </PosixApplication>
    <Application>
       <cdl:documentation>
               This element describes configuration data for application binary deployment.
       </cdl:documentation>
       <Binary>
          <cdl:documentation>
                Application binary source location at some URI.
                This element has a "type" attribute which specifys a format of the source
                file, e.g. tar or zip.
          </cdl:documentation>
       </Binary>
       <UserName>
          <cdl:documentation>
                This element is a string that defines the usar name of deployed application 
                binary on the target resource. e.g. "csmith"
          </cdl:documentation>
       </UserName>
       <GroupName>
          <cdl:documentation>
                This element is a string that defines the group name of deployed application 
                binary on the target resource. e.g. "hpc"
          </cdl:documentation>
       </GroupName>
       <Mode>
          <cdl:documentation>
                This element is a string that defines the permission of deployed application 
                binary on the target resource. String should be one to four octal digits (0-7) 
                consumed by chmod command. e.g. "755"
          </cdl:documentation>
       </Mode>
       <Pathname cdl:lasy="true">
          <cdl:documentation>
                This element is a string that describes the absolute pathname of deployed
                application binary on the target resource. It becomes available after deployment.
          </cdl:documentation>
       </Pathname>
    </Application>
    <FileSystem>
       <cdl:documentation>
               This element describes a configuration data for file system mount.
       </cdl:documentation>
        <FileSystemType>
          <cdl:documentation>
                This is a token that describes the type of filesystem of the containing
                FileSystem element.
          </cdl:documentation>
        </FileSystemType>
        <MountSource>
        </MountSource>
          <cdl:documentation>
                This element is a string that describes a remote location that mounted
                on target resource.
          </cdl:documentation>
        <MountPoint>
        </MountPoint>
        <DiskSpace>
          <cdl:documentation>
                This is a range value that describes the required amount of disc space on
                the containing FileSystem element.
          </cdl:documentation>
        </DiskSpace>
    </FileSystem>
    <HostName cdl:lasy="true">
          <cdl:documentation>
                This element is a simple type containing a single name of a host. The name 
                may refer to a single host (e.g., a machine name), a logical group of hosts 
                (e.g., a named logical group or cluster), a virtual machine, and so on.
          </cdl:documentation>
    </HostName>
    <EnvironmentVariable  cdl:lasy="true"/>
          <cdl:documentation>
                Any elements extend this element represent environment variables. Name of 
                such extended element is also name of the environment valiable and its 
                value will be available after deployment. 
          </cdl:documentation>
  </cdl:configuration>
</cdl:cdl>